{
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "Addition and Subtraction",
        "questions": [
          {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
            "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            "answer": "4"
          },
          {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What is 6 - 2?",
            "options": ["2", "5", "3", "4"],
            "answer": "4"
          },
          {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is 10 + 5?",
            "options": ["14", "15", "12", "11"],
            "answer": "15"
          },
          {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What is 9 - 3?",
            "options": ["6", "5", "4", "3"],
            "answer": "6"
          },
          {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "What is 20 + 7?",
            "options": ["27", "28", "26", "25"],
            "answer": "27"
          },
          {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "What is 15 - 8?",
            "options": ["7", "6", "5", "9"],
            "answer": "7"
          },
          {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "What is 100 + 50?",
            "options": ["150", "160", "140", "130"],
            "answer": "150"
          },
          {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "What is 25 - 10?",
            "options": ["16", "15", "14", "13"],
            "answer": "15"
          },
          {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "What is 40 + 30?",
            "options": ["70", "69", "68", "67"],
            "answer": "70"
          },
          {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "What is 50 - 20?",
            "options": ["30", "31", "29", "28"],
            "answer": "30"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
  